<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2018 Google Inc.
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~     http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <!-- App title -->
    <string name="app_name">exer2_labador_b9l</string>
    <string name="main_desc">Which Avenger Character are you?</string>
    <string name="start_desc">You are</string>
    <!-- Button label -->
    <string name="roll_label">Start</string>
    <string name="reset_label">Retry</string>
    <string name="reset_desc">Find out which Avenger character are you!</string>

    <string name="antman">
        <b>ANT MAN</b>
        \nFormer thief Scott Lang once stole an advanced size-altering
        suit in order to aid his ailing daughter, only to discover
        that the stolen tech belonged to the world-renowned Dr. Hank
        Pym. Seeing the heroic potential within him, Dr. Pym allowed
        Scott to continue using the suit, as well as the identity Pym
        once battled evil under. As the Astonishing Ant-Man, Scott now
        handles the jobs "too small" for any other Super Hero.
    </string>
    <string name="blackwidow">
        <b>BLACK WIDOW</b>
        \nS.H.I.E.L.D. Agent Natasha Romanoff, aka Black Widow (Scarlett
        Johansson), is one of the world’s greatest spies and quite
        possibly the world’s most skilled assassin. Armed with an
        extensive arsenal of specialized weapons like widow stings and
        cluster bombs, as well as a vast repertoire of martial arts skills,
        Romanoff’s unique talents make her one of director Fury’s top
        agents and an integral part in assembling The Avengers.
    </string>
    <string name="captainamerica">
        <b>CAPTAIN AMERICA</b>
        \nAfter a top secret Super-Soldier program transformed frail Steve
        Rogers (Chris Evans) into the powerful and heroic Captain America,
        his amazing WWII exploits made him a living legend. Steve saved New
        York City and turned the tide of the war, but crashed into the Arctic
        during his final mission. Awakening in the modern day, Steve learned
        that he had spent decades frozen in the icy tundra. Now, Steve Rogers
        finds himself alone in a modern world that he hardly recognizes.
    </string>
    <string name="captainmarvel">
        <b>CAPTAIN MARVEL</b>
        \nFormer Air Force pilot and intelligence agent Carol Danvers pursued
        her dream of space exploration as a NASA employee, but her life forever
        changed when she was accidentally transformed into a human-Kree hybrid
        with extraordinary powers.
    </string>
    <string name="hawkeye">
        <b>HAWKEYE</b>
        \nOne of S.H.I.E.L.D.’s most elite agents, Clint Barton (Jeremy Renner),
        code-named Hawkeye, is the greatest living marksman on Earth. Armed with
        his weapon of choice, the recurve bow, Hawkeye fires his arsenal of custom
        augmented arrows, specialized for any number of specific situations, with
        perfect precision. With the potential for global catastrophe on the horizon,
        he employs his amazing combat skills to fight along side The Avengers.
    </string>
    <string name="hulk">
        <b>HULK</b>
        \nAfter a gamma radiation experiment went awry, mild-mannered scientist Dr.
        Bruce Banner (Mark Ruffalo) found himself with a peculiar condition. When
        angered or provoked, he would transform into the uncontrollable, green-skinned
        monster known as the Hulk. Now, fearful of the damage that the Hulk could
        inflict, Dr. Banner chooses to live a discreet life in remote parts of the world,
        working to cure the sick and help the poor while trying to elude those who would
        take advantage of his ability to change into the enormous, green menace. When a
        mounting threat calls for Banner’s specialized scientific expertise, S.H.I.E.L.D.
        Director Nick Fury recruits him, knowing full well that the incredible strength
        of Banner’s alter ego, the Hulk, would be an asset to The Avengers.
    </string>
    <string name="ironman">
        <b>IRON MAN</b>
        \nOn top of being an eccentric genius, a billionaire, a playboy and a philanthropist,
        Tony Stark (Robert Downey Jr.) is also the armored super hero known as Iron Man.
        Fresh off of defeating enemies the world over, Stark reluctantly agreed to serve
        as a consultant to Nick Fury’s top-secret peacekeeping and intelligence agency
        known as S.H.I.E.L.D. Now, with a global crisis on the horizon and the fate of the
        world in the balance, Stark must again power up his Iron Man armor to save the world,
        and become a full-fledged member of The Avengers.
    </string>
    <string name="okoye">
        <b>OKOYE</b>
        \nOkoye serves with distinction as head of the Dora Milake, a ceremonial order of
        warrior women tasked with protecting the leader of Wakanda. A traditionalist at heart,
        Okoye places her duty to the king above all else, who in turn trusts her as one of his
        top advisors. With her fierce and noble spirit, Okoye is prepared to make any sacrifice
        to keep her people safe and free.
    </string>
    <string name="thor">
        <b>THOR</b>
        \nAn arrogant prince from the distant land of Asgard, Thor (Chris Hemsworth) was banished
        to Earth after his irresponsible behavior threatened his homeland. While in exile on
        Earth, Thor learned humility and helped to save his new friends from a destructive threat
        sent by his brother Loki. In the process, Thor redeemed himself in the eyes of his father,
        Odin, the King of Asgard. After being welcomed back to Asgard as a hero, Thor must now return
        to Earth once again to prevent a cosmic-level catastrophe. With Mjolnir in his hand, a
        legendary hammer with immense power, the mighty warrior soon finds himself drawn into an
        unlikely alliance with Nick Fury’s secret initiative, The Avengers, lending his power to their
        cause against his wayward brother, Loki.
    </string>
    <string name="warmachine">
        <b>WAR MACHINE</b>
        \nU.S. Air Force Colonel James "Rhodey" Rhodes has long served as both Tony Stark\'\s best
        friend and Special Liaison to Stark Industries. In battle, Rhodey dons the War Machine armor, a
        modified version of Stark\'\s own Iron Man suit. Armed with a modular Gatling cannon and enough
        firepower to take on a legion of enemies, the War Machine is a true one man army.
    </string>

</resources>
